嘿，只是因为他们说他们看见了耶稣
Hey, just because they said they saw Jesus
并不意味着他们真的做到了。
doesn't mean they actually did.
对不起。对我来说
I'm sorry. Was that for me?
也许复活的目击者...
Maybe the eyewitnesses to the Resurrection...
也许他们是妄想。你知道我的意思？
Maybe they're delusional. You know what I mean?
也许他们只是以为他们看见了耶稣。
Maybe they only thought they saw Jesus.
也许是像心智控制或洗脑一样。
Maybe it was, like, mind control or brainwashing.
Rod! Rod！
你需要看一位心理学家。
You need to see a psychologist.
哦，你觉得我有一个松动的螺丝？
Oh, you think I got a screw loose?
嗯，那是另一个故事。
Yeah, well, that's another story.
但如果你在谈论一世纪的大规模精神病，
But if you're talking about first-century mass psychosis,
你需要和心理学家交谈。
you need to talk to a psychologist.
我已经领先于你了.Rod！
I'm already ahead of you. Rod!
- 嘿我需要你找我... - 对不起
- Hey. I need you to find me... - Sorry.
一位好心理学家面试。
A good psychologist to interview.